

Blessing Krofegha

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I help build , develop , test and debug responsive designs that would stand out not just only by the interface but by the psychology , experience and professional coding indentation . I would write codes that would take the companies responsiveness and technology measures to the next level

PERSONAL DETAILS

Nationality

Nigeria

Marital status

Single

CONTACT

Bkrofegha@gmail.com

+2348028239396

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lead Frontend Developer

KUBITX August 2018 - Present

I developed the Ui/Ux Exchange wallet using React from scratch, and implemented Api's that could fetch live updates of Cryptocurrencies per time and i did that using Using Next.js.

Fullstack Developer

QUICCOURIER

June 2018 - October 2018 (Remote)

I built the tracking system that enables Users/Customers track their goods at anywhere in the the world with very explanatory analytical Dashboard

Junior Backend Developer

MYAGENT.NG

August 2017 - November 2017 (Remote)

I developed an Analytical Admin Dasnboard for real estate website that provides the owner of a property the full information and state of his/her property at every given time, with push notications, sms alerts and email notications using OOP php

EDUCATION

Advance React and Graphql

WES BOS

October 2018 - November 2018

Mobile & Web Specialist

UDACITY

January 2018 - June 2018

Web Developer Bootcamp

UDEMY

October 2016 - December 2016

TECH SKILLS



React



Node



MongoDb





Php



Vue

FRONTEND FRAMEWORKS

TEST TOOLS



Enzyme

Jest

Sass

Gatsby

Css3

Less

Bulma

Tailwind